zazzoo.com 2009-02-28

# Privacy policy - ZAZZOO USA

**Neo Network ("Company") respects your privacy, is seriously committed to protecting the privacy of its users ("Users") and has published this Privacy Policy to explain how Company treats information you submit to Company. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully prior to your access to and/or use of the Neo Network Application (the "Application") or your registration for or use of the Service (as defined in Company's Terms and Conditions of Use Agreement (the "[Terms of Use](http://www.zazzoo.com/service/terms_and_conditions)")). If you do not agree to abide by this Privacy Policy, please do not access or use the Application or register as a Member of the Application or Services. **

**By submitting information to Company, either by using the Application or registering for or using the Services, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Use. This Privacy Policy is governed by the Terms of Use, which includes all disclaimers of warranties and limitation of liabilities. All capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy will have the meaning set forth in the Terms of Use.**

  1. ACCESS TO AND USE OF THE APPLICATION AND THE SERVICES  
You represent and warrant that you are fully able and competent to enter into the terms, conditions, obligations, affirmations, representations, and warranties set forth in this Agreement. By using the Service you agree that you are eighteen (18) years of age or older. If your access or use of the Service is prohibited or restricted in any way by the laws, regulations or other governmental requirements of the jurisdiction in which you live, or if, for any reason and at any time, you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please discontinue using our Service immediately. In any case, you affirm that you are over the age of 13, as the Application and Service is not intended for children under 13. **If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use the Application or Service**.
  2. COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
You acknowledge that Company may collect and process "personal information" (i.e. information that could be used to contact you, such as full name, postal address, user name and password, phone number or e-mail address) or "demographic and usage information" (i.e. information that you submit, or that we collect, that is not personal information but necessary for the proper functioning of our Service, such as the date regarding the start and end and the extent of your usage of the Service and your personal interests and preferences), in connection with the Service. Such information collected by Company may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Company or its agents maintain facilities. By using the Service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Company makes no representation or warranty with respect to any duty to permanently store any personal information you may provide. By using our Services and providing us with personal information, you waive any claims that may arise under your own or any other local or national laws, rules or regulations or international treaties. We may from time to time, transfer or merge your personal information collected off-line to our online databases or store off-line information in an electronic format. We may also combine personal information we collect online with information available from other sources, including information received from our advertisers and promotional partners. This Privacy Policy applies to your personal information for as long as your personal information is in our possession, even if you terminate or discontinue your use of the Service.
  3. CHANGE OR UPDATE REGISTRATION DATA  
You may request a change to or update the Registration Data you provide Company by changing your profile in the ["Edit Profile" section of your personal page](http://.zazzoo.com/profile/edit) or by contacting Company via email [info@zazzoo.com](http://www.zazzoo.com/service/open_form/info/change_data) (please include in the Subject line the words "Change in Registration Data"). It is your responsibility to maintain and promptly update the Registration Data to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. 
  4. USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
Company uses your personal information to identify you and, in some cases, to improve and customize the content you see on the Application. Your personal information may also be aggregated and used by Company for market research, project planning, troubleshooting problems, detecting and protecting against error, fraud or other criminal activity, to enforce the Terms of Use or any applicable Rules, for other internal purposes, and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. Company will obtain your consent for any use of your personal information beyond those set forth in this Privacy Policy and the original uses for which you provided your consent.   
You agree that Company may use personal information about you to analyze Application usage, improve or customize Company's Services, customize the Application's content, and as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy. You also agree that Company may use your personal information to contact you. Unless you specifically opt out, you also agree that Company may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Application or the Services. By accepting the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information, unless you specifically opt out in applicable circumstances.  
Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in SMS text messages and chat areas, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your username (not your email address) may be displayed to other Users when you upload content or send messages through the Application. Any content that you submit to the Application may be redistributed through the Internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.
  5. DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
Except as expressly provided herein, absent your prior consent, Company does not share your personal information with any unrelated third parties. Additionally, Company does not permit unrelated third parties to perform "reverse searches" whereby they could identify users from mobile telephone numbers or email addresses. In addition, the following describes some of the ways that your personal information may be disclosed in the normal scope of business to provide you with the Services: 
    * _Profile._ Company may post certain information as a part of your User Profile, which will be viewable by other Users and visitors to the site, including but not limited to your username, age, location, and sexual orientation. Company will not disclose your home address, email address, phone number, or full name in connection with your User Profile.
    * _Advertisers._ Company may aggregate personal information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, Company does not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally without your explicit consent.
    * _External Service Providers._ There are a number of separate services offered by third parties that Company refers to as external service providers that may be complementary to your use of the Application or the Services. If you choose to use these separate services, disclose information to the external service providers, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their privacy policy. With your consent, and for your convenience, Company may provide some of your personal information to an external service provider offering such services. To prevent Company's disclosure of your personally identifiable information to an external service provider, you can decline such consent or simply not use their services. Because Company does not control the privacy practices of these third parties, you should evaluate their practices before deciding to use their services.
    * _Internal Service Providers._ Company may use third parties that Company refers to as internal service providers to facilitate or outsource one or more aspects of Company's business, products and Services that Company provides to you and, therefore, Company may provide some of your personal information directly to these internal service providers (e.g. customer care). In some instances, the internal service provider may collect information directly from you. In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the internal service provider. If you provide additional information to an internal service provider directly, then their use of your personally identifiable information is governed by their applicable privacy policy.
Notwithstanding the foregoing, Company reserves the right, and you authorize Company, to share or disclose your personal information, including, without limitation, any content, records or electronic communications of any kind, when Company determines, in its sole discretion, that the disclosure of your personally identifiable information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against you if: 
    * you are or may be violating the Terms of Use, this Privacy Policy or any applicable Rules; 
    * you are interfering with Company's or a third party's rights or property;
    * you are violating any applicable law, rule or regulation;
    * necessary or required by any applicable law, rule or regulation; and/or 
    * requested by governmental authorities in the event of any investigation, act of terrorism or instance of local, regional or national emergency.
In addition, Company cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example, without limiting the foregoing, Company may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access your transmissions or communications. Therefore, although Company uses industry standard practices to protect your privacy, Company does not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private. However, Company shall use reasonable commercial and legal efforts to protect its users' information and to maintain the privacy and anonymity of Members and users.  
In the event of a merger, acquisition, sale of substantially all of its assets or change of control of Company, personal information collected by Company about you will be considered a business asset and will be transferred to the applicable new entity.
  6. OPT OUT PROCEDURE  
We may post notices, offers, advertising and promotional material on our Service and we may use your personal information to contact you by e-mail or text message or otherwise to promote our Service or to send you offers we believe may be of interest. You may choose to opt out of receiving marketing and promotional e-mails, text or other electronic messages from us by either (i) sending an SMS text to our short number, 82582 (or other number we designate on our website), (ii) calling our customer service representatives at 1-800-491-7495 or (iii) sending us an e-mail at [help@zazzoo.com](http://www.zazzoo.com/service/open_form/help). If you are using SMS, you must unsubscribe separately to each active text alert or other Service you are enrolled in by using our Service keywords (you can find these on our Website) which must be a combination of ONLY (i) the Service name keyword and (ii) the word "OFF." We may always contact you via e-mail or SMS for administrative or informational purposes, including follow-up messages regarding the administration of your subscription, any promotions you have entered or participated in, offers you have accepted or Services you have enrolled in or ordered or any of your transactions related to our Service.   
If we unknowingly send an e-mail or SMS text message to anyone under the age of 18 or who has registered in violation of our Terms of Use, that individual's parent or guardian has the right to unsubscribe or direct us to opt out that individual from receiving future e-mails, SMS text messages, text alerts or e-newsletters or request termination of any registration, subscription or use of our Service.
  7. PARENTS OF MINORS  
Parents or guardians of children under the age of 18 have the right to immediately terminate or cancel their child's use of our Service. A parent or guardian should notify us by contacting us at [help@zazzoo.com](http://www.zazzoo.com/service/open_form/help) and provide verifiable identification that they are the child's parent or guardian. We will use the same verification and authentication procedures for the parent or guardian, however, minors (under the age of 18) are not permitted to use our Service and their information must and shall be deleted once their age and parent are verified. We always reserve the right to deny, suspend, deactivate, terminate and cancel any registration, subscription, username and the use of or access to any or all of our Service, if we believe there is a question about the identity of the person trying to use our Service. We may decide not to provide you access to your personal information. In such cases, we may provide you with an explanation of why access cannot be provided and a contact person for further inquiries. 
  8. SECURITY  
Personal information you submit to Company is password protected for your privacy and security. In the unlikely event that an unauthorized third party compromises Company's security measures, Company will not be responsible for any damages directly or indirectly caused by an unauthorized third party's ability to view, use or disseminate such information.
  9. LINKS TO THIRD PARTIES  
The Application may include links to third party websites or mobile applications. Such links are not an endorsement by Company of those websites or mobile application and/or the products or services offered on those websites or mobile applications. Third party websites or mobile applications may have different privacy policies, and Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of those third party websites or mobile applications. If you click on a link to a third party website or mobile application, Company encourages you to check the privacy policy of that website or mobile application, as it may differ substantially from that of this Privacy Policy. Company makes no representations or warranties nor is Company responsible for the privacy policies of any website or mobile application other than the Application. If you decide to access any third party links appearing on the Application, you do so at your own risk. 
  10. TRANSMISSIONS, SUBMISSIONS AND POSTINGS  
Company welcomes the submission of comments, information and feedback regarding the Application and the Services. However, Company does not want to receive certain kinds of information from you, including any confidential or proprietary information, without prior written consent of Company. Although Company does not regularly review your transmissions, submissions or postings, Company reserves the right (but not the obligation), at its sole discretion and at any time, to edit, refuse to post or remove your transmissions, submissions or postings. You hereby acknowledge and agree that Company may review transmissions, submissions or postings made by you to determine, in its sole discretion, your compliance with the Terms of Use, this Privacy Policy and any applicable Rules, and that Company shall have the unrestricted right to use such information for any purpose and without compensation to you.
  11. OTHER TERMS  
To review other applicable terms and conditions that apply to this Privacy Policy, including, without limitation, intellectual property rights, disclaimer of warranties, limitation of liability and resolving disputes, please review the [Terms and Conditions](http://www.zazzoo.com/service/terms_and_conditions).
  12. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
Company reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to update, amend and/or change this Privacy Policy without prior notice and at any time. Updates to this Privacy Policy will be posted here. You are encouraged to revisit this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to review any changes that have been made. Your continued use of the Application and any Services following the posting of any such changes shall automatically be deemed your acceptance of all changes. 
  13. CHILDRENS' PRIVACY  
Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Company does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the Application from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our Application is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Application at any time or in any manner. If Company learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the Application without verified parental consent, then Company will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 
  14. SPECIAL NOTE TO INTERNATIONAL USERS  
The Application is hosted in the United States. If you are a User accessing the Application from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Application, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Notice, and our [Terms of Use](http://www.zazzoo.com/service/terms_and_conditions), you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. 
  15. IN THE EVENT OF MERGER, SALE, OR BANKRUPTCY  
In the event that Company is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, or sells all or substantially all of its assets, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information and content we have received and collected from our Users and Members as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used. 
  16. QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS  
If you have questions, comments, concerns or feedback regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via any of the methods set forth below:   

    * Via email: [info@zazzoo.com](http://www.zazzoo.com/service/open_form/info)
